Add URL to Hotspot
Select desired hotspot area
Next, assign "URL" type to hotspot area
Input Title
Enter any URL website
Choose to open URL in 'Same Window' or a 'New Tab'
Click the "preview" button on the top right
Preview CTA hotspot area to ensure it functions correctly
Now you can access the website you entered
Link to Vinmobi site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinMobi”
Choose a VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click the "preview" button
Open the Preview window
Click hotspot area you created
Now you can access the Vinmobi site you choose
Link to VinDesk site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinDesk”
Choose a VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click the "preview" button on the top right
Now you can access the VinDesk site you choose
That's it! You've successfully assigned a URL to your hotspot area.
Explore more features and enhance your projects with VinCTA.